{
    "id": "618254e44f1a49e98220f29cb804e9cd",
    "title": "Articles Or No Articles",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "1772533005a94a7f97082d979993e113",
            "title": "Articles Or No Articles",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He died …………………….",
                    "description": "No article is used in this expression.",
                    "answers": [
                        "at sea",
                        "at the sea",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I met some interesting people at ……………………….",
                    "description": "In American English, university is usually used with the article 'the'. In British English, 'the' can be omitted before university. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "university",
                        "the university",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He left …………………………….. in the morning and never came back.",
                    "description": "No article is used before home. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "home",
                        "the home",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I regret leaving ………………………….. at fourteen.",
                    "description": "No article is used in the expression leave school. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "school",
                        "the school",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will meet you at ……………………………",
                    "description": "We use the article here because the college is just a meeting place.",
                    "answers": [
                        "college",
                        "the college",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was surprised at the amount of ……………………………. collected.",
                    "description": "'The' is dropped after ‘the amount of’.",
                    "answers": [
                        "money",
                        "the money",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He went to ……………………………… in Cambridge.",
                    "description": "No article is normally used in this expression.",
                    "answers": [
                        "college",
                        "the college",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is time the children went to …………………………..",
                    "description": "No article is used in the expression 'go to bed'.",
                    "answers": [
                        "bed",
                        "the bed",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I didn’t feel like getting out of …………………………",
                    "description": "No article is used in this expression.",
                    "answers": [
                        "bed",
                        "the bed",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is collecting money for …………………………….",
                    "description": "The blind means all blind people. The article ‘the’ is required in this expression.",
                    "answers": [
                        "blind",
                        "the blind",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………………… criminals are non-violent.",
                    "description": "When most means the majority of, it is used without the.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Most",
                        "The most",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He could play …………………………. when he was just five.",
                    "description": "Articles are always used with the names of musical instruments.",
                    "answers": [
                        "piano",
                        "the piano",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}